mycolorstreet.com 2019-08-01

# Privacy Policy - Color Street

## privacy policy

* * *

Color Street, LLC (“Company”, “us”, “our” or “we”) value your concerns about privacy and want to make sure you feel comfortable using our websites. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect, how we use the information, and with whom we share it. We also describe the measures we take to protect the security of the information and how our customers can contact us about our privacy practices. Please note that this Privacy Policy governs information collected at any Company sites, including social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter, and instagram, and information collected via email, surveys, promotions, and rating & review.

**Types of information collected**

There are two types of information collected: (a) personally identifiable information and (b) non-personally identifiable information.

**(a) Personally identifiable information**

is information that identifies you as an individual, such as your name, address, telephone number, credit card number, birth date, email address, profile information, and purchase history. Personal information is provided voluntarily. You may choose not to provide personal information, but in order to use certain services on Company sites, such as to make a purchase or participate in a promotion, you may be required to provide your personal information.

**(b) Non-personally identifiable information**

does not identify you specifically. This information may consist of your browser type, IP Address, the URL of the previous web site you visited, device information, operating system, mobile network, advertising identifier, location information, etc. Non-personally identifiable information does not identify you personally.

**How information is collected**

When you visit and use any Company sites, information may be collected (1) passively and (2) directly.

**(1) Passive Information Collection**

You may not know that certain information is collected when you interact with Company’s sites. This information may consist of IP address-related information, system Media Access Control address, network configuration information, network device information, browser plug-in type and versions, operating system, and information related to your geographic location. Cookies or web beacons may be used to collect information passively. This information may be collected whether you are signed in to Company’s sites or not. Please note that information that is collected passively may identify you personally.

**(2) Direct Information Collection**

Information may be collected directly from you when you choose to use certain services on this site and any other Company’s sites. This information may be collected in the following instances, including but not limited to: when you make a purchase, create an account, sign-up for emails and catalogs, use social media applications, and participate in sweepstakes, contests and promotions. These are examples of how we may collect personally identifiable information from Company sites. If you do not want us to collect your personally identifiable information, please do not provide it on Company sites.

**(3) Third Party Web Analytics Services**

The Company site may use one or more third party web analytics services. Such third party services include Google Analytics which collect data via Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers, in addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation. We make every effort to adhere to third party analytics policies. By using Google Analytics advertising features, we are required to disclose the following.

This site may employ Google Analytics Advertising features. This site and other third-party vendors may use first-party cookies or other first-party identifiers, and third-party cookies or other third-party identifiers together. Visitors to our out site can opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features used, including through Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means.

**How we use information we collect**

We may use information about you and also share with our affiliates and vendors who perform services on our behalf. Here are some examples of how we may use your personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information: to fulfill your orders and send you information about your transactions, process credit card payments, to tell you about our products and offers, to personalize your experience, to conduct marketing analysis and to send you surveys or newsletters, to combine the personally identifiable information you provide us with other personal and non-personally identifiable information about you, and to allow you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions. Please note that some of our social media applications may share information collected through those apps. In addition, we may disclose information about you, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. We may also disclose information about you when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual fraudulent or illegal activity.

**Links to and from other sites**

The Company sites may contain links to and from other websites or applications, including those of our partners, advertisers, merchants and other sites. These sites are not maintained by Company and have their own privacy policies and information collection practices. Company is not responsible for the practices of other such websites, and disclaims all liability associated with your use of, and the content on, other sites.

**Consent to transfer**

The site is maintained in the United States of America. If you are located outside of the United States, any information you provide to us may be transferred to the United States where our databases are maintained. By using the sites, you consent to this transfer. Although we take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected, please be aware that the United States may not provide the same level of protection for your personal information as the one in which you reside.

**Children’s Privacy**

Company sites are not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children. If you are under 13 and would like to make a purchase, please ask a parent or legal guardian to place the order for you. Children under 13 are not permitted to make a purchase, create an account, enter a promotion, submit a customer survey, sign-up for emails or post comments.

**Changing, Updating or Deleting Personal Information**

You can update, change or delete certain personally identifiable information (such as your email address, mailing address and payment method).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

By visiting and using the sites, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Company reserves the right to change, modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. We will post the revised policy here, which at that time will be effective immediately.

**Assignment**

In the event that all or part of our assets are sold or acquired by another party, or in the event of a merger, you grant us the right to assign the personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information collected via the Sites.

**Governing Law**

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the state of New Jersey, excluding without resort to its conflicts-of-law principles. Please note that your use of Company sites may be subject to other local, state, national, and international laws. You expressly agree that exclusive jurisdiction for any claim or dispute with Company or relating in any way to your use of Company sites lies in the state and/or federal courts of New Jersey, and you further agree and expressly consent to the exercise of personal jurisdiction in the courts of New Jersey in connection with any such dispute including any claim involving us, Company sites, our affiliates, subsidiaries, employees, contractors, officers, directors, telecommunication providers, and/or content providers.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy practices, you may contact us by completing the contact form on this site. Any comments or feedback you provide shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Company shall be free to use such information on an unrestricted basis.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding Company's disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us.
